let questions = [
{
    numb: 1,
    question: "If the base sequence in DNA is 5' AAAT 3' then the base sequence in mRNA is:",
    answer: "C. 5'AAAU3'",
    options: [
      "A. 5'UUUU3'",
      "B. 3'UUUU5'",
      "C. 5'AAAU3'",
      "D. 3'AAAU5'"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Avery, MacLeod and Mc Carty used the S(virulent) and R (avirulent) strains of streptococcus pneumoniae. They isolated and purified protein, DNA, RNA from the bacteria and treated them with related enzymes. They concluded that :",
    answer: "A. DNA was transforming agent",
    options: [
      "A. DNA was transforming agent",
      "B. RNA was transforming agent",
      "C. Protein was transforming agent",
      "D. All are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Identify the characteristic which is not applicable to the genetic code:",
    answer: "A. Non-Polar",
    options: [
      "A. Non-Polar",
      "B. Non-Overlapping",
      "C. Commaless",
      "D. Universal"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Ribose is differentiable from deoxyribose in having:",
    answer: "C. Hydroxyl group at 2nd carbon",
    options: [
      "A. Two extra oxygen",
      "B. No oxygen",
      "C. Hydroxyl group at 2nd carbon",
      "D. One extra hydrogen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A DNA strand is directly involved in the synthesis of all the following except:",
    answer: "D. Protein",
    options: [
      "A. Another DNA",
      "B. t-RNA & m-RNA",
      "C. r-RNA",
      "D. Protein"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The genes are responsible for growth and differentiation in an organism through regulation of:",
    answer: "D. Translation and transcription",
    options: [
      "A. Translocation",
      "B. Transformation",
      "C. Transduction and translation",
      "D. Translation and transcription"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Genetic information is carried out by long chain molecule made up of:",
    answer: "C. Nucleotides",
    options: [
      "A. Amino acids",
      "B. Enzymes",
      "C. Nucleotides",
      "D. Histone proteins"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Anticodons are found in:",
    answer: "B. tRNA",
    options: [
      "A. mRNA",
      "B. tRNA",
      "C. rRNA",
      "D. In all"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following element is not found in nitrogenous base?",
    answer: "D. Phosphorus",
    options: [
      "A. Nitrogen",
      "B. Hydrogen",
      "C. Carbon",
      "D. Phosphorus"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Transfer of genetic information from a polymer of nucleotides to a polymer of amino acids is:",
    answer: "C. Translation",
    options: [
      "A. Replication",
      "B. Transcription",
      "C. Translation",
      "D. Reverse transcription"
    ]
  },
 ];